Ghilman Faza

UI/UX Designer

% +6285155020756

www.ghilmanfaza.site

Sleman, Yogyakarta

Summary

I started as a UI/UX designer for 2 years while studying at the Indonesian Islamic University in the Informatics Study Program. have critical thinking on a problem and have high enough creativity to do a job. I have skills that are able to compete in the field of design and programming. My expertise is Design Research, UI/UX Design, Mobile & Web UI Design.

Experience

Freelance UI/UX Designer

2021 - Present

Remote

I started my career as a UI/UX Designer as a direct freelancer with clients. I freelance when someone needs a design for a website or mobile that has an attractive interface and comfortable user experience, I am comfortable working remotely.

Alterra Academy X Kampus Merdeka - Malang, East Java, Indonesia

Feb 2022 - Aug 2022

UI/UX Designer

Learn various ui/ux design materials from basic to advanced stages and produce various interfaces from mobile design to web design. Searching and finding problems in Inarisk Personal app and redesigning them for case studies using the design thinking method. Become a UI/UX Designer in a team in a capstone project to create various needs such as userflow, wireframe, low fidelity, high fidelity to prototypes in the form of mobile app designs for users and web app designs in the form of landing pages and dashboards for admins.

Information System Development Team

Sep 2021 - Jan 2022

Big Project In Informatics At The Islamic University Of Indonesia

Responsible as a coordinator in making web designs for admins in the form of a dashboard display that is used to set the system in the tutorial application. Moreover acting as a front end developer to help implement the design results that have been made into a web

UX Club Team - Islamic University Of Indonesia

Oct 2020 - Nov 2021

Challenge UX Club Islamic Univesity Of Indonesia

Learn the basics of ui/ux design and share insights about user experience and user interfaces. Completing challenges given by ux club to add to portfolio such as designing interfaces for ecommerce and music player mobile apps.

Intelligent Decision Support System Team

Mar 2021 - Jul 2021

Big Project In Informatics At The Islamic University Of Indonesia

Assist the community in making decisions by using an intelligent system that is carried out by the Simple Additive Weighting (SAW) method. Built a web design interface with dashboard view and survey as main features in this big project

Website-Based Application Development Team

Sep 2020 - Jan 2021

Big Project In Informatics At The Islamic University Of Indonesia

Responsible as a coordinator in making web designs and conducting research to find the latest innovations based on the needs of the community and similar competitors. Create low fidelity and high fidelity to enhance the developed web design

Education

Organization

Coordinator Creative Information And Publication Of Laboratory Assistant

Oct 2020 - Oct 2022

Laboratorium Informatika UII

Deputy Coordinator For Supplies, Publications, Decoration And Documentation

Feb 2021 - Feb 2022

Unisi Music Community

Licenses & Certification

Certificate MSIB Kampus Merdeka - Alterra Academy

2022

Certificate of English Proficiency Test

Dec 2022 - Dec 2024

Cilacs UII, Total Score 511

Tools & Skills

Mobile Design	Bootstrap	Wireframing	Maze
Web Design	Android Studio	Prototyping	HTML/CSS
UI/UX Design	Figma	Social Media Content Creation	Product Design